(Leonard:)I can't decide whether I want Stan Lee
to autograph...
(Leonard:)...my Journey Into Mystery 83,
first appearance of Thor...
...or my Fantastic Four Number 5,
first appearance of Dr. Doom.
["FINAL JEOPARDY!" THEME
PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
Alex, I'm gonna go with:
"What is you're a dumb-ass?"
[RASPBERRY
PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
(Sheldon:)I've decided I'm going to have Mr. Lee
sign my copy of this month's Batman.
(Howard:)That's crazy. Stan Lee
had nothing to do with Batman.
(Sheldon:)Which is why no one else
will ask him to sign one.
I'll be the possessor of a unique,
albeit confusing artifact...
(Sheldon:)...which will set me apart from
the hoi polloi of comic-book fandom.
That's a great idea. I'm gonna get him
to sign a Batman as well.
What is it about the word "unique"
you don't understand?